ABOUT ME

I am currently enrolled as a student of the Rithm School. My goal is to be a software engineer upon completion. Prior to this, I worked as an underwriter in commercial real estate finance. I believe my analytical background will prove useful for problem-solving in programming.

CONTACT

- (i) jenniferma93@gmail.com
- (626) 688-8099
- jenniferhm.github.io

San Francisco, CA



SKILLS

- Web Development: basic
 JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and
 Adobe Dreamweaver
- Risk Analysis
- Problem Solving
- Delegation
- Decision Making
- Customer Service

JENNIFER H. MA

ASPIRING SOFTWARE ENGINEER

EDUCATION

RITHM SCHOOL

(San Francisco, CA: 7/2019 – expected 11/2019) Full-Stack Web Development

UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA (USC)

(Los Angeles, CA: 8/2011 – 5/2015)
Bachelor of Science, Business Administration
Minor in Real Estate Development

WORK EXPERIENCE

BANK OF THE WEST, BNP PARIBAS GROUP

(Los Angeles, CA: 8/2015 – 4/2019)

Vice President, Senior Credit Products Officer (9/2017 – 4/2019) Assistant Vice President, Credit Products Officer (2/2017 – 9/2017) Credit Analyst (8/2015 – 2/2017)

- Underwrote commercial real estate transactions ranging in size from single bank middle market deals (min. \$10 million) to large corporate syndications (over \$100 million) for sophisticated clients including publicly traded REITs.
- Managed a credit portfolio aggregating over \$700 million.
- Performed financial and credit risk analysis on Sponsors including balance sheet, income statement, and cash flow analysis, stress testing, and projections.
- Worked closely with other departments (e.g. Capital Markets, Loan Administration, Compliance) to manage risk of complex financial products and services.
- Mentored and trained new analysts in financial and real estate analysis concepts.

USC TRANSPORTATION

(Los Angeles, CA: 8/2011 – 8/2014)

Customer Service Associate

- Engaged in sales and fulfillment processes of permits for visitors, students, staff, and faculty.
- Communicated iwth over 30 customers each dahy to resolve various parking citation and delinquincy issues.
- Facilitated the training of new studnet workers and assisted in administrative responsibilities.